Where the truth lies.
The Dry is a crime, thriller, mystery film directed by Robert Connolly.
Aaron Falk returns to his drought-stricken hometown to attend a tragic funeral.
But his return opens a decades-old wound - the unsolved death of a teenage girl.
Aaron Falk, played by Eric Bana.
Gretchen Schoner, played by Genevieve O'Reilly.
Greg Raco, played by Keir O'Donnell.
Scott Whitlam, played by John Polson.
Grant Dow, played by Matt Nable.
McMurdo, played by Eddie Baroo.
The Dry is a 2020 Australian mystery drama thriller film directed by Robert Connolly, from a screenplay by
Connolly and Harry Cripps, and is based on the 2016 book of the same name by Jane Harper.
The film stars Eric Bana, Genevieve O'Reilly, Keir O'Donnell and John Polson.
The film had its premiere in Melbourne on 11 December 2020, before Roadshow Films released the
film in Australia on 1 January 2021, and received positive reviews from critics.
IFC Films released the film in the United States on 21 May 2021.
A sequel based on Harper's 2017 follow-up book, Force of Nature, was later announced to be in
production in 2022, titled Force of Nature: The Dry 2, and was released on 8 February 2024.
The film explores themes of australia, small town,
drowning, based on novel or book, funeral.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending and intense.